A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 300 Latin America - Series 833 Lebanon FA387b
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Chile, 1940-1973; 309; 45 box(es)
  - Chile - Social Sciences, 309.S
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, January - July 1962 (Box 36, Folder 293)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, August - December 1962 (Box 36, Folder 294)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 295)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 296)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, January - August 1965 (Box 36, Folder 297)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, September - December 1965 (Box 36, Folder 298)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, January - June 1966 (Box 37, Folder 299)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, July - December 1966 (Box 37, Folder 300)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 301)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 302)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, 1970-1972 (Box 37, Folder 303)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics - Jaspersen, Frederick Z. - (Tufts University), 1966 (Box 37, Folder 304)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Morales, Mariela - (Travel Grant), 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 305)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Rodreguez, Amalia - (Travel Grant), 1965-166, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 306)
    - Chile - Catholic University - Economic Research Center, 1956, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 329)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Economics, 1956, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 330)
    - Chile - Economic Research - ("Teoria Economica") - (Grunwald, Joseph) (Box 42, Folder 332)
    - Chile - Economic Research - (Grunwald, Joseph), 1940-1965 (Box 42, Folder 333)
    - Chile - Economic Research, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 334)
    - Chile - Economic Research, January 1958 (Box 42, Folder 335)
    - Chile - Economic Research, April-June 1958 (Box 42, Folder 336)
    - Chile - Economic Research, June-September 1958 (Box 42, Folder 337)
    - Chile - Economic Research, January-June 1959 (Box 42, Folder 338)
    - Chile - Economic Research, September 1959 (Box 43, Folder 339)
    - Chile - Economic Research, October-December 1959 (Box 43, Folder 340)
    - Chile - Economic Research, September-December 1960 (Box 43, Folder 341)
    - Chile - Economic Research - (Publication # 23-24) (Box 43, Folder 342)
    - Chile - Economic Research - (Publication # 25-26) (Box 43, Folder 343)
    - Chile - Economic Research - (Publication # 27-28) (Box 43, Folder 344)
  - Chile - Virus Studies, 309.V
    - Chile - University of Chile, 1961-1962 (Box 38, Folder 307)
    - Chile - University of Chile, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 308)
    - Chile - University of Chile - Contreras, Guillermo - (Travel Grant), 1964 (Box 38, Folder 309)
- Colombia, 1944-1975; 311; 88 box(es)
  Nine subseries as follows: 311 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 311 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 311 C Nursing (nursing education, public health nursing) 311 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 311 E Fellowships, scholarships, training awards 311 R Humanities and arts 311 S Social Sciences 311 V Virus Studies 311 W Schistosomiasis
  - Colombia - General (No Program), 311.GEN
    - Agriculture - (Minutes), 1949-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Agriculture, 1947-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3-6)
    - Agriculture, 1952-1956 May (Box 2, Folder 7-11)
    - Agriculture, 1956 June 1956-1959 December (Box 3, Folder 12-17)
    - Agriculture, 1960-1965 (Box 4, Folder 18-23)
    - Agriculture, 1956 January-1970 December (Box 5, Folder 24-26)
    - Agriculture - Administration, 1949-1954 (Box 5, Folder 27-30)
    - Agriculture - Administration, 1955-1958 (Box 6, Folder 31-36)
    - Agriculture - Administration, 1959 January-1960 September (Box 7, Folder 37-43)
    - Agriculture - Administration, 1960 October-1962 April (Box 8, Folder 44-50)
    - Agriculture - Administration, 1962 May-1963 December (Box 9, Folder 51-57)
    - Agriculture - Administration, 1964 January-1965 February (Box 10, Folder 58-63)
    - Agriculture - Administration, 1965 March-1966 September (Box 11, Folder 64-70)
    - Agriculture - Administration, 1966 October-1968 June (Box 12, Folder 71-76)
    - Agriculture - Administration, 1968 July-1973 December (Box 13, Folder 77-81)
    - Agriculture - Agreements - (Minutes) (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Agriculture - Agreements, 1949-1953 (Box 13, Folder 82A, 83)
    - Agriculture - Agreements, 1954-1962, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 84-86)
    - Agriculture - Agreements - Supplements (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - Agriculture - Donation of Equipment, 1959-1962, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - Agriculture - Staff House, 1959-1961, 1965, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 89-90)
    - Agriculture - Supplies and Equipment, 1968-1971 (Box 15, Folder 91)
    - Agriculture - Guzman-Naranjo, Julia - (Travel Grant), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 92)
    - Cali Medical School - Kruse, Cornelius W. - (Travel Grant), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 93)
    - Cali Medical School - Ortiz, Elva Leonor - (Travel Grant), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 94)
    - Colegio Bolivar, 1968-1971 (Box 15, Folder 95)
    - Columbus School, 1954-1956 (Box 15, Folder 96)
    - Cuadros, Alvaro - (Population), 1967 (Box 15, Folder 97)
      Related Archival Materials note
      cross-reference - Cali-Bogota, Colombia - October 15-November 7, 1963 - Hard-1 (Charles Hardin) - Box 81, Folder 759
    - Hunter, Alice S., 1961 (Box 15, Folder 98)
    - National School of Hygiene, 1946, 1948-1950, 1952, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 99-100)
    - New Granada, 1954-1958, 1968-1970 (Box 15, Folder 101)
      cross-reference - Todaro, Michael - "Diary of a trip to Colombia" - November 29-December 5, 1970 - TOD - Box 81, Folder 760
    - Toro, Libardo - (Engineering), 1963 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - University of Antioquia - Jaramillo, Lucrecio, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    - University of Antioquia - Library School, 1955-1958 (Box 16, Folder 104-109)
    - University of Antioquia - Library School, 1959-1961 (Box 17, Folder 110-115)
    - University of Antioquia - Library School, 1962-1964 (Box 18, Folder 116-122)
    - University of Antioquia - Library School, 1965-1971 (Box 19, Folder 123-128)
    - University of Antioquia - Library School - Visits, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 0128A)
    - University of Antioquia - Medical Library, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 0128B)
    - University of Del Valle - Administrative Service, 1962-1965 (Box 20, Folder 129-132)
    - University of Del Valle - Administrative Service, 1966-1970 (Box 21, Folder 133-134)
    - University of Del Valle - Administrative Service - Carroll, Augustus J. - (Travel Grant), 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 135)
    - University of Del Valle - Arellano Angel, Hernando - (Travel Grant), 1967 (Box 21, Folder 136)
    - University of Del Valle - Automobile, 1961-1962, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 137)
    - University of Del Valle - Basic Studies - Faculty, 1963-1965 (Box 21, Folder 138)
    - University of Del Valle - Carmona, Rafael, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 139)
    - University of Del Valle - Castro O., Jose Mildred, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 140)
    - University of Del Valle - Ellis, Elmer - (Travel Grant), 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 141)
    - University of Del Valle - Faculty Recruitment, 1965, 1969, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 142)
    - University of Del Valle - Faculty Salary Supplements, 1962, 1965-1967, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 143)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff, 1964-1969 (Box 22, Folder 144-150)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff, 1970-1973, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 151)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff - Supplemental Material - (Anthropology) (Box 23, Folder 152)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff - Supplemental Material - (Geography) (Box 23, Folder 153)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff - Supplemental Material - (History) (Box 23, Folder 154)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff - Supplemental Material - (Political Science) (Box 23, Folder 155)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff - Supplemental Material - (Psychology) (Box 23, Folder 156)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff - Supplemental Material - (Sociology) (Box 23, Folder 157)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff - Buttrey, Jerold, 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 158)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff - Dixon, James C., 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 159)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff - (Goslinga, Cornelis), 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 160)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff - (Ramsey, Russell), 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 161)
    - University Del Valle - Florida Staff - (Webber, Irving L.), 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 162)
    - University Del Valle - Ghitis Blanco, Alberto - (Travel Grant), 1961-1963 (Box 24, Folder 163)
    - University Del Valle - Inter-American Course on Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 164)
    - University Del Valle - Ocampo Londono, Alfonso - (Travel Grant), 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 165)
    - University Del Valle - Palacios M., Graciela, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 166)
    - University Del Valle - Sanabria, Adela - (Travel Grant), 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 167)
    - University Del Valle - Seminars, 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 168)
    - University Del Valle - Sullivan, Dan A. - (Visiting Professor, Geology), 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 169)
    - University Del Valle - Survey Team, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 170)
    - University Del Valle - Student Cafeteria, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 171)
    - University Del Valle - Toxicology Laboratory, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 172)
    - University of the Andes - Arts and Sciences Program, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 173)
    - University of the Andes - Library, 1959-1963 (Box 25, Folder 174)
    - University of the Andes - Restrepo Hoyos, Jorge, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 175)
    - University of the Andes - Zuluaga, Julio - (Travel Grant), 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 176)
    - University of the Andes - Agudelo, Gilardo, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 177)
    - Cali Medical School, 1950-1955 (Box 25, Folder 178-179)
    - Cali Medical School, 1956-1958 May (Box 26, Folder 180-186)
      Cali Medical School - 1957 - "The Annals" - Box 82, Folder 775
    - Cali Medical School, 1958 June-1959 December (Box 27, Folder 187-191)
    - (Hardin, Charles M.) - (Trip Diary: Cali - Bogota, Colombia), October 15-November 7, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 759)
    - (Todaro, Michael P.) - (Trip Diary), November 29-December 5, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 760)
    - Agriculture, 1951-1970 (Box 81, Folder 761-763)
    - Agriculture - Administration, 1950-1965 (Box 81, Folder 764)
    - Agriculture - Agreements, 1949-1961 (Box 81, Folder 765)
    - Agriculture - Donation of Equipment, 1969-1970 (Box 81, Folder 766)
    - Agriculture - Staff House, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 767)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Administrative Services, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 768)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Faculty Salary Supplements, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 769)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Florida Staff - (Ramsey, Russell) (Box 81, Folder 770)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Survey Team, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 771)
    - University of Antioquia - Library School, 1957-1963 (Box 82, Folder 772-773)
    - University of Antioquia - Medical Library, 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 774)
  - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 311.A
    - Cali Medical School - Acevedo, Carlos Alberto - (Travel Grant), 1965 (Box 27, Folder 192)
    - Cali Medical School - Aqudelo, Gildardo - (Travel Grant), 1969 (Box 27, Folder 193)
    - Cali Medical School - Aquirre Castano, Alfredo - (Travel Grant), 1965 (Box 27, Folder 194)
    - Cali Medical School - Alvarez Gutierrez, Jose Raul - (Travel Grant), 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 195)
    - Cali Medical School - Araujo Grau, Jorge - (Travel Grant), 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 196)
    - Cali Medical School - Bernal, Matilde, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 197)
    - Cali Medical School - Biochemistry - (Colas Espada, Antonio), 1956-1958 (Box 28, Folder 198)
    - Cali Medical School - Borrero, Luis Maria - (Travel Grant), 1956-1957, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 199)
    - Cali Medical School - Bueno Montana, Miguel - (Travel Grant), 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 200)
    - Cali Medical School - Calonje, Julio H. - (Travel Grant), 1963 (Box 28, Folder 201)
    - Cali Medical School - Canosa, Cipriano Antonio - (Travel Grant), 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 202)
    - Cali Medical School - Chaux, Aurelio - (Travel Grant), 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 203)
    - Cali Medical School - Cobo, Edgard - (Travel Grant), 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 204)
    - Cali Medical School - Cobo, Alex - (Travel Grant), 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 205)
    - Cali Medical School - Colas, Antonio - (Travel Grant), 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 206)
    - Cali Medical School - Cuardardo, Eliseo - (Travel Grant), 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 207)
    - Cali Medical School - Cuadros, Alvaro - (Travel Grant), 1960, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 208)
    - Cali Medical School - Electron Microscope Training, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 209)
    - Cali Medical School - Epidemiology Conference, 1958-1960 (Box 28, Folder 210-212)
    - Cali Medical School - Escobar Soto, Jorge - (Travel Grant), 1966 (Box 29, Folder 213)
    - Cali Medical School - Exchange Program, 1958-1961 (Box 29, Folder 214)
    - Cali Medical School - Experimental Medicine, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 215-220)
    - Cali Medical School - Experimental Medicine, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 221)
    - Cali Medical School - Family Health Service, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 222)
    - Cali Medical School - Franco Henao, Argemiro - (Travel Grant), 1958-1959 (Box 30, Folder 223)
    - Cali Medical School - Gaitan, Eduardo - (Travel Grant), 1961-1962, 1964-1965, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 224-225)
    - Cali Medical School - Ghitis, Jacobo, 1962-1963, 1967, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 226)
    - Cali Medical School - Gongora, Elizabeth - (Travel Grant), 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 227)
    - Cali Medical School - Gracian Casado, Miguel, 1956-1957 (Box 30, Folder 228)
    - Cali Medical School - Gutierrez, Yezid, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 229)
    - Cali Medical School - Guzman L., Carlos - (Travel Grant), 1960 (Box 30, Folder 230)
    - Cali Medical School - Hoffman, Ernesto O. - (Travel Grant), 1963-1966 (Box 30, Folder 231)
    - Cali Medical School - Hospital, 1956-1959 (Box 30, Folder 232)
    - Cali Medical School - Hospital, 1966-1970 (Box 31, Folder 233-234)
    - Cali Medical School - Hospital - Personnel, 1959-1961 (Box 31, Folder 235)
    - Cali Medical School - Hunter, Thomas H., 1964 (Box 31, Folder 236)
    - Cali Medical School - Isaza, Jaime - (Travel Grant), 1959-1960 (Box 31, Folder 237)
    - Cali Medical School - Jaramillo, Robert - (Travel Grant), 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 238)
    - Cali Medical School - Lehmann V., F. Carlos, 1955-1956 (Box 31, Folder 239)
    - Cali Medical School - Leon, Carlos A. - (Travel Grant), 1961 (Box 31, Folder 240)
    - Cali Medical School - Library, 1953-1957 (Box 31, Folder 241)
    - Cali Medical School - Llanos, Guiliermo - (Travel Grant), 1965 (Box 31, Folder 242)
    - Cali Medical School - Lopez Villegas, Alfonso - (Travel Grant), 1961-1964 (Box 31, Folder 243)
    - Cali Medical School - Lourido, Eduardo - (Travel Grant), 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 244)
    - Cali Medical School - Matallana, Alfonso - (Travel Grant), 1964 (Box 31, Folder 245)
    - Cali Medical School - McGill, Henry C. Jr., 1956-1958 (Box 31, Folder 246)
    - Cali Medical School - Medical Records, 1956-1959, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 247)
    - Cali Medical School - Medina, Pablo - (Travel Grant), 1966 (Box 32, Folder 248)
    - Cali Medical School - Montoya Ochoa, Juan Antonio - (Travel Grant), 1954-1958 (Box 32, Folder 249)
    - Cali Medical School - Ocampo, Alfonso - (Travel Grant), 1957-1961 (Box 32, Folder 250)
    - Cali Medical School - Orozco, Guillermo - (Travel Grant), 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 251)
    - Cali Medical School - Pediatrics - Ordway, Nelson K., 1964 (Box 32, Folder 252)
    - Cali Medical School - Physiology, 1959-1962, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 253)
    - Cali Medical School - Physiology - Barlow, George, 1959-1961 (Box 32, Folder 254)
    - Cali Medical School - Physiology - Swann, H. G., 1958-1962 (Box 32, Folder 255)
    - Cali Medical School - Postgraduate Training, 1959-1962 (Box 33, Folder 256)
    - Cali Medical School - Reproductive Physiology, 1964-1970 (Box 33, Folder 257-259)
    - Cali Medical School - Restrepo, Carlos - (Travel Grant), 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 260)
    - Cali Medical School - Robertson, William B. - (Travel Grant), 1966 (Box 33, Folder 261)
    - Cali Medical School - Rojo Fernandez, Vincente - (Travel Grant), 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 262)
    - Cali Medical School - Salazar-Navarro, Hernando - (Travel Grant), 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 263)
    - Cali Medical School - Sanmartin, Carlos - (Travel Grant), 1959-1960, 1964-1966 (Box 33, Folder 264)
    - Cali Medical School - Tatum, Howard J., 1956-1958 (Box 34, Folder 265)
    - Cali Medical School - Tropical Medicine, 1960-1966, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 266-270)
    - Cali Medical School - Velaquez Palau, Gabriel, 1957-1958, 1965, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 271)
    - Cali Medical School - Velez-Gil, Adolfo - (Travel Grant), 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 272)
    - Cali Medical School - Visits, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 273)
    - Cali Medical School - Wahner, Heinz - (Travel Grant), 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 274)
    - Cali Medical School - Zambrano, Ernesto - (Travel Grant), 1964-1966 (Box 35, Folder 275)
    - Cali Medical School - Zuleta Carrasquilla, Hernan - (Travel Grant), 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 276)
    - Candelaria Health Center, 1966, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 277)
    - Colombia Association of Faculties of Medicine, 1962-1972 (Box 35, Folder 278-281)
      cross reference - Colombia Association of Faculties of Medicine - 1964 - Bulletin - Box 83, Folder 784
    - Colombia Association of Faculties of Medicine - Supplemental Material (Box 36, Folder 282-284)
    - Colombia Association of Faculties of Medicine - Seminars, 1963-1965 (Box 36, Folder 285)
      cross reference - Colombia Association of Faculties of Medicine - Bulletin, 1970 - Box 83, Folder 785
    - Colombia Association for the Scientific Study of Population, 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 286-287)
    - Javeriana University - Biochemistry, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 288)
    - Javeriana University - Library, 1960-1963 (Box 37, Folder 289)
    - Javeriana University - Medical School, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 290)
    - Javeriana University - Microbiology, 1964-1966 (Box 37, Folder 291)
    - Javeriana University - Morphology, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 292)
    - National University of Colombia - Medical School, Bogota - Equipment, 1953-1958 (Box 37, Folder 293)
    - National University of Colombia - Renjifo, Santiago, 1959-1962 (Box 37, Folder 294)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Hemodynamics Research, 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 295)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Nutrition Conference, 1956-1958 (Box 37, Folder 296)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Ospina, Lucero - (Travel Grant), 1969 (Box 37, Folder 297)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Pedraza, Miguel, 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 298)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Pharmacology, 1968-1971 (Box 37, Folder 299)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Pradilla, Alberto - (Travel Grant), 1968 (Box 38, Folder 300)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Renal Physiology, 1968-1970 (Box 38, Folder 301)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Rural Medical Care, 1969-1971 (Box 38, Folder 302)
    - Universidad Del Valle - Water Systems, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 303)
    - University of the Andes - Cell Physiology, 1957-1964 (Box 38, Folder 304-305)
    - University of the Andes - Genetics, 1958-1962 (Box 38, Folder 306)
    - University of the Andes - Hunter, Francis Robert - (Travel Grant), 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 307)
    - University of the Andes - Grose, Elizabeth S., 1958 (Box 38, Folder 308)
    - University of the Andes - Luque, Orlando de, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 309)
    - University of Antioquia - Arango, Francisco - (Travel Grant), 1961-1963 (Box 38, Folder 310)
    - University of Antioquia - Biochemistry, 1958-1960 (Box 39, Folder 311)
    - University of Antioquia - Biology, 1958-1961 (Box 39, Folder 312)
    - University of Antioquia - Bojanini, Emilio, 1956-1959 (Box 39, Folder 313)
    - University of Antioquia - Botero, Jaime - (Travel Grant), 1956, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 314)
    - University of Antioquia - Cespedes, Aurelio, 1962-1964 (Box 39, Folder 315)
    - University of Antioquia - Duque, Oscar, 1956-1958 (Box 39, Folder 316)
    - University of Antioquia - Epilepsy, 1955-1958 (Box 39, Folder 317)
    - University of Antioquia - Gomez Arango, Alberto, 1955-1956 (Box 39, Folder 318)
    - University of Antioquia - Jimenez, Bernando, 1955-1956 (Box 39, Folder 319)
    - University of Antioquia - Latorre Restrepo, Guillermo, 1956-1957 (Box 39, Folder 320)
    - University of Antioquia - Microbiology, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 321)
    - University of Antioquia - Neurophysiology, 1959-1961 (Box 39, Folder 322)
    - University of Antioquia - Obstetrics, 1956-1958 (Box 39, Folder 323)
    - University of Antioquia - Pelaez Botero, Jesus, 1954-1956 (Box 39, Folder 324)
    - University of Antioquia - Perez Upequi, Pablo, 1956-1958 (Box 39, Folder 325)
    - University of Antioquia - Physiology, 1954-1957 (Box 39, Folder 326)
    - University of Antioquia - Surgery, 1961-1964 (Box 40, Folder 327)
    - University of Antioquia - Velez, Hernando, 1956-1958 (Box 40, Folder 328)
    - University of Antioquia - Velez A., Hernan - Travel Grant, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 329)
    - University of Caldas - Travel Grant, 1957-1958 (Box 40, Folder 330)
    - University of Caldas - Exchange Program, 1958-1963 (Box 40, Folder 331)
    - University of Caldas - Hematology - Aranzazu, Ferry, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 332)
    - University of Caldas - Medical Library, 1958-1961 (Box 40, Folder 333)
    - University of Caldas - Microbiology, 1959-1962 (Box 40, Folder 334)
    - University of Caldas - Physiology, 1960-1962 (Box 40, Folder 335)
    - University of Caldas - Training, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 336)
    - University of Caldas - Orozco Ospina, Hernando - Travel Grant, 1957-1958 (Box 40, Folder 337)
    - University of Cartagena - Biochemistry, 1958-1960 (Box 40, Folder 338)
    - University of Cartagena - Library, 1958-1960 (Box 40, Folder 339)
    - University of Cartagena - Parasitology, 1956-1958 (Box 41, Folder 340)
    - Velazquez, Gabriel, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 341)
    - Vergara Delgado, Jorge, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 342)
    - Colombian Nurses' Congress, 1963-1965 (Box 41, Folder 343)
    - Public Health - Murillo, Maria Teresa - Travel Grant, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 344)
    - Sister Carmen Aguilera - (Nursing Education), 1964 (Box 41, Folder 345)
    - Cali Medical School, 1955, 1957-1959 (Box 82, Folder 775)
    - Cali Medical School - Araujo Grau, Jorge, December 12, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 776)
    - Cali Medical School - Epidemiology Conference, 1958, 1959 (Box 82, Folder 777)
    - Cali Medical School - Experimental Medicine, 1959-1961 (Box 82, Folder 778)
    - Cali Medical School - Hospital, 1956, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 779)
    - Cali Medical School - Physiology - Swann, 1959-1961 (Box 82, Folder 780)
    - Cali Medical School - Reproductive Physiology, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 781)
    - Cali Medical School - Visits, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 782)
    - Colombian Association for the Scientific Study of Population, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 783)